This yogurt is a Bulgarian yogurt that is non fat so it really healthy, it is a little more on the sour side as far as yogurts go and most middle eastern yogurt is kind of sour.
I would recommend using the middle eastern yogurt if you can on the hummus because this taste more better then the regular yogurt that you get in HEB.
You can usually find this at HEB but if cant go to your middle eastern store and they would have yogurt and you just want to add about 2 tablespoons to your hummus.
Not only this gives it a great flavor but it also makes the hummus a little liquidly and not as chunky as it would be if it didn't have this.
A lot of people use olive oil in there hummus to make it a lot thinner then what it usually is because when you grind up all these garbanzo beans it comes out kind chunky.
It's a lot better to get it more puree that way it has a better texture to it.
This yogurt as I said is non fat it also comes in a version that is not non fat that you can pick which ever one you like but it is definitely very good yogurt.
This one right here is my favorite and I think it is whitemountainfoods.
com you can go and order this.
I will definitely recommend getting this kind of yogurt so so good.
Yogurt in the middle east is kind of like ketchup here in the United States so and that is it for the yogurt part of the hummus.